Wynkoop Family Papers
Wynkoop family Papers
- Restricted material
  - Miscellany (Box 6)
Hotchkiss & Lewis 1850 Sep 25, New Haven, to William A. Judson & Co.
Houseal, Bernard Michael 1777 Feb 21, New York, to John Brunkhurst
Jackson, Henry 1795 Jun 1?, Flatbush, to Augustus Wynkoop
Jansen, Cornelius 1796 Jun 14, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop
Judah, Julia M. (Gelston) 1882 Oct 6, Brattleboro, to Henry Reynolds 1882 Oct 20,, to Sarah B. Reynolds
Kern, John Michael 1776 Jan 14, [no place], to [no recipient] 1776 Jan 21, Hanover [N.Y.], to [no recipient]
Laidle, Archibald 1761 Sep 24, Flushing, to the Consistory of the Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York (contemporary copy)
Lansingh, Myndert 1747 or 8 Jan 13, Curacao, to James Alexander
Lasker?, John 1791 Jun 25, New York, to Cornelius Wynkoop
Loomis, Josephine S.? 1890 Jan 1, Saint Paul, to Mrs. Wynkoop 1892 Mar 6, Saint Paul, to Mrs. Wynkoop
McMillan, John 1788 Dec 12, Albany, to Cornelius C. Wynkoop 1792 Jul 20, Albany, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1798 Dec 24, Albany, to Cornelius Wynkoop
Morris, Woodbury 1761 Mar 28, Providence, to Nicolas DeRonde
Myers, Margaret Jane 1833 Mar 18, Mobile, to Margaret Reynolds
Quackenboss, Walter 1761 Jun 2, New York, to Catharine Rypel
Reade, D[e]Witt & Livingston 1748 Sep 20, Kingston, to [Jamaica] Mary Alexander 1748 Oct 5, Kingston, to [Jamaica][Mary Alexander]
Reynolds, Henry Hinsdale 1853 Jun 9, [no place], to W. Hathaway
Reynolds, J.T. 1903 Jul 22, Media, Pa., to Sarah B. Reynolds 1903 Jul 31, Media, Pa., to Sarah B. Reynolds
Reynolds, Julia 1882 Apr 19, Reynoldsville, Pa., to Mrs. M.J. Myers
Reynolds, Sarah B. 1891 Apr 21, Kingston, to Jonathan [no surname] 1894 Jul 3, Kingston, to Dr. Edward [Judson Wynkoop] 1894 Sep 18, Kingston, to Dr. Edward [Judson Wynkoop]
Silvester, John L.B. 1905 Dec 7, Albany, to Sarah B. Reynolds
Silvester, P. [Peter?] 1771 Jul 25, Albany, to George Peterson 1796 Jul 9, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop
Stanton, Gerald N. 1894 Nov 10, New York, to Edward J. Wynkoop 1894 Nov 10, New York, to Francis S. Wynkoop 1894 Nov 17, New York, to Edward Judson Wynkoop 1895 Apr 30, New York, to Sarah [B. Reynolds] 1895 May 5, New York, to Sarah [B. Reynolds]
Tappen, Christopher 1795 Sep 11, Kingston, to Edward Livingston
Tappen, Christopher et al. 1794 Mar 13, Kingston, to Edward Livingston
Tolman, Thomas 1778 May 18?, Albany, to Edward Livingston 1779 Mar 9, Albany, to Edward Livingston
Van Buren, Martin 1856 Jan 22, Lindenwald, to [Samuel Hawley?] 1856 Feb 8, Lindenwald, to [Isaac Isaacs?]
Van Buren, Martin, Jr. 1853 Jan 15, [no place], to [Jane (Hawley) Isaacs] 1853 Mar 14, [no place], to Mrs. [Jane] I[saacs] 1853 Jul 2, [Killarney], to Mrs. [Jane] I[saacs] 1853 Jul 13, Glasgow, to I[saac] S. Isaacs 1854 Jun 4, Sorrento, to Isaac S. Isaacs
Van Dyck, C.V.A. 1890 Apr 9, Beirut, to Sarah [Reynolds?]
VanSchaack, P. 1818 Mar 31, Kinderhook, to Augustus Wynkoop
Van Wyck, Jas. P. 1904 Jun 27, Hudson, N.Y., to [Sarah B.] Reynolds
Werden, Isaac 1764 Feb 15, Quebec, to Cornelius C. Wynkoop 1764 Jun 10, Quebec, to [Cornelius C.?] Wynkoop 1765 Feb 16, Quebec, to [Cornelius C.?] Wynkoop
Wetsel, Mary Christina 1801 Mar 18, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop, with copy of 18 Apr 1801 letter of Cornelius Wynkoop, to Peter Sim [1802] Nov ?], [no place], to Cornelius Wynkoop 1803 Jan 9, [no place], to Cornelius Wynkoop 1803 Dec 13, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1804 May 19, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop
Wheelwright, Nat[haniel?] 1763 Aug 15, Boston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1763 Aug 22, Boston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1763 Aug 29, Boston, to Cornelius Wynkoop
Williams, Hen[ry?] 1775 Jan 19, New York, to Cornelius C. Wynkoop
Wynkoop, A[drian?] 1769 Apr 1, Hurley, to [Cornelius C. Wynkoop?]
Wynkoop, Augustus 1791 Dec 27, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Apr 7, to 1795 Sep 27, Brooklyn, to Cornelius Wynkoop
Wynkoop, Cornelius 1763 Jan 14, New York, to William Ward 1763 Nov 22, New York, to [Maria Katherina (Ruehl) Wynkoop?] 1771 Oct 24, New York, to Peter Silvester 1773 Mar 31, New York, to Peter Silvester (copy) 1787 Jul 3, Red Hook, to Herman Hoffman 1796 Sep 24, New York, to Jonathan Hasbrouck 1800 Jul 3, New York, to Daniel Hasbrouck 1800 Jul 7, New York, to Jonathan Hasbrouck [no date], [no place], to Rutger Bleeker
Wynkoop, Cornelius C.(b. 1772) 1790 Jun 18, Kinderhook, to Cornelius & Catharine Wynkoop 1790 Jul 19, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1790 Oct 26, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Jul 18, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Jul 24, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Aug 5, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Sep 1, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Sep 9, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Sep 21, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Sep 30, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Oct 3, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Oct 15, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Oct 16, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Oct 28, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Nov 4, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Nov 7, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Nov 16, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Nov 26, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Dec 1, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Dec 28, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Feb 9, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Mar 4, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Mar 14, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Mar 23, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Mar 31, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Apr 7, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Apr 11, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Apr 28, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Sep 29, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Oct 6, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Oct 23, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Nov 2, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Nov 19, Kingston, to Augustus Wynkoop 1792 Nov 30, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1793 Jan 28, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1793 Feb 4, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1793 Feb 4, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1794 Jan 22, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1794 Feb 20, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1794 May 3, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1794 May 23, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1794 Jun 19, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1794 Jul 10, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1794 Oct 9, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1794 Dec 7, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1794 Dec 22, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Jan 12, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Jan 27, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Feb 2, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Apr 27, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 May 3, Kingston, to Henrietta Wynkoop 1795 May 6, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Jun 1, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Jun 22, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Aug 31, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Sep 30, Kingston, to Augustus Wynkoop 1795 Nov 28, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Nov 30, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Mar 24, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1796 Jan 12, Kingston, to Augustus Wynkoop 1796 Mar 30, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop
Wynkoop, Cornelius C.(b. 1772) et al 1794 Mar 13, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1796 Apr 20, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop
Wynkoop, Edward Judson 1894 Jul 6, Hudson, N.Y., to [Sarah B.] Reynolds 1894 Sep 7?, Syracuse, N.Y., to [Sarah B.] Reynolds
Wynkoop, Francis S. 1894 Nov 13, New York, to Sarah [B. Reynolds]
Wynkoop, Henrietta 1894 Aug 1, Kingston, to Augustus Wynkoop
Wynkoop, John C. 1788 Oct 23, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1789 Jul 7, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1789 Jul 18, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1789 Aug 26, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1789 Sep 16, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1789 Nov 16, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1790 Feb 4, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1790 Mar 8, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1790 May 8, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1790 Jun 17, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1790 Jul 20, [no place], to Cornelius Wynkoop 1790 Sep 8, Kinderhook, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Jul 10, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Jul 16, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Aug 5, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Sep 2, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Sep 8, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Sep 21, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Oct 3, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Oct 14, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Nov 4?, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Nov 15, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1791 Nov 16, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Feb 4, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Feb 9, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Mar 13, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Mar 22, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Mar 31, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Apr 11, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Apr 14, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Apr 28, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Jul 21, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Aug 14, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Sep 17, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Sep 26, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Sep 29, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Oct 5, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1792 Nov 20, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1793 Dec 2, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1794 Aug 7, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Jan 26, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Mar 27, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Apr 20, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Jun 8?, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Oct 13, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Oct 22, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1795 Nov 9, Kingston, to Edward Livingston 1795 Nov 30, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1796 Apr 20, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1796 May 12, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1796 May 13, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1796 May 14, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1796 May 23, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1796 Jun 2, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1796 Jun 8, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1796 Jun 23, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop 1796 Jul 6, Kingston, to Cornelius Wynkoop
Wynkoop, Lea 1795 May 9?, [no place], to [Cornelius ? Wynkoop] 1796 Dec 5, [no place], to Henrietta Wynkoop 1797 Jun 30, [no place], to Cornelius Wynkoop 1799 Jul 27, [no place], to Cornelius Wynkoop [no year] Apr 16, [no place], to Cornelius Wynkoop [no year] Oct 25, [no place], to Cornelius Wynkoop
Wynkoop, M.W. 1829 Oct 6, Ghent, to Eliza Kittle
Wynkoop, Peter Silvester 1804 Jan 1, Kingston, to Augustus Wynkoop
Wynkoop, Richard 1894 Sep 14, Brooklyn, to [Sarah B.] Reynolds
Yeomans, Moses [no date], [no place], to Cornelius C. Wynkoop